Let me wish you a Happy Wonderful Year.
Good morning!
Viewers all over the world. Happy Wonderful Year!
I call it a Wonderful Year because it is a wonderful year.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
This year is a wonderful year.
I know many nations have not entered the New Year.
But I want to tell you what you are about to enter
or what you have entered, is a wonderful one.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
And those nations that have a different calendar ... but in all, 2017 is a wonderful year!
It is so wonderful for you, people of God!
After going through the whole thing, the revelation and what we should be expecting in the year,
you will agree with me, so wonderful!
I don't know how to call it.
Will I call it New Year or New Beginning or whatever, but I chose the word wonderful.
Because it is so wonderful.
It demands 'trust and obey'.
The year demands 'trust and obey'.
That's why I said it is wonderful.
It is a wonderful year because of what it demands.
If you want to go through the year, enjoy the year, overcome and walk through it smoothly,
just trust and obey;
that is why I call it a wonderful year.
This year, we will experience challenges and some of these challenges are going to be unique.
When something is unique, there will be things that you will not know how to handle
because you have never gone through them before.
They are not things you can handle.
Things you can handle, when they come you say, "Hey, yes, let me apply the former tactic, stragegy
I used in the past", but the one that is very unique, you will say,
"I don't know how to go about this; how will I do it, oh God".
A lot of these challenges will be very unique - different from what you know and are used to.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Remember that yesterday I told you that
no matter the challenges, they will not impair you but improve you - just trust and obey.
The reason there will be so many challenges and unique ones is because there is a dream for you.
Today, take my word - you have a dream.
Tell your neighbour, "I have a dream".
A dream is something that you may not know but people can tell you, "You have a dream".
You say, "What is the dream?"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This year will come with so many challenges and unique ones because you have a dream.
There is something the Lord said to me that I should tell you -
the voice of their wailing shall be silenced.
That is, tell your people - the voice of their wailing will be silent.
This means that God is there to intervene and to rescue you.
The outcome of this is a dream - dream of breakthrough -
the outcome of challenges.
You have nothing to worry about - just trust and obey.
The Lord says, "The voice of trouble shall be silenced".
What else again?
The voice of difficulty shall be silenced.
The voice of setback, hardship, just name them, shall be silenced.
It means these will come: You will only hear the crying but they will not reach you.
Amen!!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Voice means strength - their strength and ability to destroy and kill you will be combatted.
Just trust and obey.
Tell your neighbour, "Just trust and obey".
Those dreams you thought were lost, are not lost.
There are a lot of dreams you had in the past, and you keep asking yourself,
"I dreamt I gave handshake to this man 3 years ago, but I have never met the man till now".
There are a lot of questions you keep asking yourself but you don't know what to answer.
Those dreams are not lost.
Amen!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This year, dream of breakthrough - a new dream for you.
Amen!!
Write it down.
I'm just giving you the summary of what is here.
Dream of breakthrough - a new dream for you.
Amen!
Just trust and obey.
Amidst trouble, in the midst of challenges, you will find yourself
but the Lord says, "The voice of challenges shall be silenced!"
Amen!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The outcome of the temptation and difficult circumstances you will be going through,
the outcome of the unique challenges you will be going through -
dream of breakthrough, a new dream for you.
A new dream for you.
Amen!!
Dream of prosperity - a new dream for you.
Are you writing it down?
MESSAGE TITLE: A NEW DREAM FOR YOU
These are the dreams you are supposed to have yourself.
But you could not, but I had the dream and I am now telling you what I dreamt about you.
If you now doubt my dream, definitely, then there is no cause for you to come here.
Can somebody come out and tell me what dream you had about yourself, concerning this new approach.
You are saying Happy New Year without dream, how come?
How do you know you are a in new beginning? Can somebody? How do you know?
Oh no, this is intellectual property anyway...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Is it a slogan? It's not a slogan, it has to do with your life.
If you say, "New Year, New beginning", you should believe -
your soul and spirit should believe it.
When your soul believes it, then, it will work for you.
It's not a slogan.
Talk to me.
How do you know you are in a New Beginning, in a New Year? Can somebody tell me?
Praise The Lord. You know that you are in a New Year when you have a change in mind, change of mind,
change of position, wanting to do things differently from how you used to do them before
and as soon as you have this feeling and you believe it, you begin to do things in that new way
and that makes you a new person and a new creature.
Not just change in calendar, but change in position and change in what you believe in - to a new thing.
Ok, thank you. Can we believe that this is what you read, or this is what you believe.
I have never read it, but I believe it.
You believe it?
I believe it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ok, tells us those things that you have changed, to start the New Year?
Well, basically I am a business man and...
Ahhh...
Can you see where this man started from. Sit down, sit down. I know, I know you people.
First, money.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You begin a new year when you finally discover that everything you don't want
and you don't like - unfavourable situations - end with the year.
Ask your neighbour, "What are unfavourable situations that have ended with the year 2016?"
Ask your neighbour, "What are those unfavourable situations you have been in
that have ended with that year?"
Carry-over is not good. You were fighting yesterday, you still wake up and the fight continues.
"Happy New Year 2017!" - the fight continues. You have not begun a New Year. You're still in 2016.
Every unfavourable situation you have been in, must end with the outgoing year.
That is how we know.
The way you were thinking yesterday, is the same way you are thinking now;
the same way you approached things yesterday
is the same way you are approaching things now - what is new then?
The same anger, pain, envy, jealousy, offence, bitterness, strife - those qualities are still there;
it is not too late now.
And right now, we are in the House of God at the beginning of that year. What a wonderful year!
This is why I call it "Wonderful Year".
Let me tell you something. Assume this year did not start on a Sunday like last year?
You know where you were last year. You were with friends.
You know the 1st January is the time you use to visit friends, go for tourism,
which is opposite to where we are now.
Look at where you find yourself.
The approach you give to this year is so wonderful -
the best approach one can give is to trust and obey.
So this is why we are here today.
It is not too late to settle our accounts on the 1st of January.
Are you ready?
That has to do with your heart.
Blessed are the pure in heart; they shall settle their accounts.
Tell your neighbour, "Blessed are the pure in heart; they shall settle their accounts".
That is, you will see God, you will have a new beginning, you will have a new dream.
I want to take you back again. The revelation I have for you. Are you ready to listen now?
Just listen and write it down.
I was in a vision and the Lord gave me a dream for you.
You may excluse yourself, you may include yourself -
it is a matter of faith.
They say, "Yes, this man is talking to me" or "No, this man is not talking to me".
It is a matter of choice.
The Lord revealed to me that this year will come with unique challenges, so many challenges.
Tell your people, they should believe and trust;
just trust and obey.
Are you writing it?
Just trust and obey.
The Lord said, "Remember, I am the Father of dreams".
He started telling me some of the people He had given dreams.
"I am sending you to your people; give them this dream".
He said He gave a dream to Abraham,
a dream to Daniel,
a dream to Joseph,
a dream to Peter and I woke up.
When I woke up, I said "What is this?" I realized that, oh no, this is the Voice from Heaven.
The vision continued.
Here are dreams - dream of walking with the Lord, a new dream for you.
Whether you like it or not,...this year... don't just delay... something will propel you -
the unique challenges, which you will know yourself that no witchdoctor will help you,
No fake people, spiritualists or whatever, can help you.
You will know yourself, you will be convinced beyond resonable doubt that no one can help you.
Let me run to God.
You will run a proper run to God this year.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There will be a force you cannot resist.
Dream of walking with the Lord - a new dream for you this year, 2017.
I can't hear you.
You have not started. When you leave here, you will see what will be happening in your life.
By the time you leave here, you will start seeing a force you cannot resist.
You want to pray and fast the more.
The more the attack, the more you pray and fast this year.
You have been serving God in the past intellectually. That is how you serve God.
That will not work this year.
You will serve God with all your heart this year. That is a new dream for you.
The more the challenges, the more your desire for God this year.
So, the challenges we are talking about are a blessing.
It's a blessing then.
Whatever challenges T.B. Joshua is talking about are a blessing
because the more the challenges, the more my desire for God.
It's a blessing. Let it come! I want to draw closer to God.
If that will draw me closer to God, it's a blessing!
So, now, there is no cause for fear.
Before now, when challenges come, in the past 2016, you begin to run helter skelter.
Running to spiritualists, running to this, running to that. Spending money; being afraid; fear.
Running from God instead of running to God.
It's a good year.
I know you are asking yourself, "How would this happen? How would my desire for God happen?"
Because when trouble comes, you always panic. You say, "Ah, how will I get out of this trouble?"
Rejoice.
This year - I don't know how it will happen.
The Vision I saw for you, number ONE:
Dream of walking with the Lord - a new dream for you.
Amen!
A new dream has come. Happy New Year!
Nothing and nothing will stop you from the love of God this year.
Amen!
No challenges will stop you from the love of God.
No difficult circumstances can stop you from the love of God.
Amen!
No infirmity will stop you from the love of God.
The more they come, the more your desire for God, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Stand up and give thanks to God!
The aim and objective of satan is to separate you.
He uses challenges and difficult circumstances to separate you,
to bring you into sin, to confess him. This is just the aim of satan.
But his aim has been defeated! The more they come, the more your desire.
The more the challenges, trouble, sickness, infirmity - just name those things satan can bring -
the more they come, the more your desire and determination for God.
His aim has been defeated.
Be strong; trust Him. That is the key to begin this year.
When I had this vision, I was happy. Immediately I stood up, I said, "Lord, thank you".
This is what I have been praying for.
This is what has been rescuing me. This is the tactic and strategy that has been protecting me.
The more these people come, the more my desire.
The more these people attack, the more my desire and my determination.
The more they hate me, the more my desire and determination.
The more people speak bad of me, the more my desire and determination. This has been protecting me.
When satan realises that the more he attacks you, the more your desire for God, he will leave you.
That is satan for you.
At the beginning of this year, it may be a bit rough.
But when he realises that, this person, I cannot separate this person with challenges.
No matter the sickness, this person will not deny God.
No matter the difficult circumstances coming to this man, he will not...
Look at what happened to Job. The more he afflicted this person, the more he loved Jesus.
He'll just say, "Oh, this one is not one of us. Let him just..." He will leave you.
But the moment he realises that when he hits you, you look back.
It is not possible to look back to answer your enemy and at the same time continue the journey.
"Look at". "What are you saying?"
Where are you going then?
Where am I going now? I am going nowhere.
I go nowhere. That is the journey you have been walking with the Lord.
That is your journey with the Lord.
Come, brother; come here please.
Let me show you what I am talking about. This is God. Stand here.
I don't want to use anybody for satan.
I don't want to.
We are in a New Year.
This is satan here. Can you see?
Can you see? Ok. Here is this foolish man
Here, you. You represent T.B. Joshua and this is God. This is where you are going.
You are on the way, and this hit, when he hits you; it's either disappointment or failure
or setback
or sickness. Something.
This is... he can't just hit you without these...... nightmares
You're just going, just going... he'll just hit you. When he hits you, you'll say, "Aha aha".
You know you're going, you cannot see this place (where you're going).
This is where you'll concentrate.... "Aha, aha".
This is where you're going. "Aha, aha". Can you see? Where am I going now?
That is the journey you have embarked on.
His interest is to cause you your position,
to overthrow you and to cause you setback and limitation.
See where I am going, instead of going straight.
You will not be able to run a straight race.
Now, here satan hit me. The journey I have embarked on. This is me, T.B. Joshua.
If he hits me, I will be talking, praying to fight satan, but I will not look back.
I'm fighting, but I continue my journey.
That is why you are here today.
If this journey had not been a straight race, you would not be here today.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You would not be here today.
Your business has not been a straight race.
Your finances have not been a straight race.
Your marriage has not been a straight race.
This is why you have to run a straight race.
The more satan hits you, the more you should speed up your spiritual walk.
A hit of satan is like you are climbing a hill on a bike.
When you are climbing the hill on the bike, you put it on a smaller gear so it can move.
The more you are hit, either sickness or disease, that does not make you a child of satan.
You can be sick in body and yet be a child of God. Continue your race.
It is what the Lord said now.
A new dream of walking with the Lord - a new dream for you.
Amen!
You may be seated. Thank you.
MESSAGE TITLE: A NEW DREAM FOR YOU
When these attacks are not coming, your dream cannot come.
It is your dream that attracts the challenges.
If there is no dream, there are no challenges.
No dream, no challenges.
Dream of walking with the Lord - if there is no dream of walking with the Lord, there are no challenges.
So, you are happy concerning new dream, but it attracts challenges.
So my brother,
when challenges come, remember your dream and your goal.
Nothing can be compared with your dream and your goal.
TWO: Don't forget what I said. It was not a message, it was a vision.
Your wailing will be silenced.
The voice of trouble, difficulty, setback shall be silenced!
Their voices shall be silenced!
Write it down.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hmm, yes. It shall be silenced.
This will begin to manifest from June.
From January to June, you should be ready to fight.
Challenges, difficulties from now till June. But by June...
When you trust and obey, satan will know that you cannot be separated. He will leave you alone.
All over the world. I am not talking to any particular nation. All over the world.
Those who are under the influence of my voice.
Viewers, you are under the influence of my voice. Write it down, it will guide you.
It's a guide to help you throughout this year.
If you can do that, satan will soon know that you are not the type to be disturbed,
to be separated from God. He will soon know.
But satan has not yet known. He still believes he can separate you from God.
That is why he keeps pushing you. He knows you will soon follow him and renounce God.
Let him know nothing can separate you from the love of God.
Can hardship, sickness, infirmity, setback, poverty, humiliation or temptation? Nothing!
Talk to your God right now.
Nothing can make me look back! Nothing can separate me!
Nothing, yes. Talk to your God.
They will come with their humiliation, challenges, setback, disease and sickness!
They will come; let them come!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Amen!
Dream of walking with the Lord - that means there will be grace for you, inner grace.
Oh My God, My God, My God.....
The SCOAN Sunday Service
All you lack and all you want, your business is not going well; your health is not ok.
Who owns your health? Who owns your business?
Do you know God is richer than your dreams?
He will put everything in place.
I will not use the word, "Congratulations"; I will say, "At last, a new dream has come!"
Amen!!
You may be seated.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So, you are blessed. Do you have any questions before we go further?
You have a question?
It is not really a question. You have just been speaking about me.
For 5 years 7 months I have been in the bush fighting to come here, and this is my coming.
And all you have been speaking is about me.
For the past 5 years you have been trying to come?
Yes, 5 years 7 months. Drinking once, eating once at the mountain.
Until this time around, I've managed to come here.
I saw God. I saw Him.
Ah, you cannot see God. You'll only hear His instruction.
Something might have gone wrong somewhere. Sometimes, when we do not have proper discretion.
Because, God has given us discretion. That discretion, He does not tamper with.
He gives us the right to speak our mind.
But there could be wrong discretion.
We need to be in a proper state, to act with God.
If you are not in a proper state to act with God, you need someone to intervene.
To be an intermediary between you and God.
How many years did you say you spend on the mountain?
5 years 7 months.
My God. I need to see you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Something has gone wrong somewhere.
And while you were in the mountain, you were eating?
It was drinking once and eating once. These were the instructions.
Eating once?
I was eating once since 2002.
At what time?
20:00 hrs.
Ah, ok. I want to see my brother. Like I said, God is so much concerned about us.
Most especially, when you have family.
He will not now carry you from your family and put you in the mountain for 5 years.
What of the family at home, wife and children?
Our God is so concerned about us. He loves us so much.
Just like He loved all His Apostles.
So that's why I'm concerned that the "God" you're talking about carried you to the mountain for 5 years,
the family is at home, the children are at home and you are eating once, what would the family eat?
And you are the breadwinner of the family. I think something is wrong somewhere.
Things were not normal.
No. I was putting on green ... I didn't have anywhere to stay.
I used to wear green ladies trousers and pink ladies trousers.
Don't worry, sir. I understand that something has happened. That's what I'm saying.
Everything will be alright. That is why we are here.Thank you.
Ok, any other questions?
Let's ask our mummy here.
You have a question? Ok.
So these challenges will only attack us but not kill us?
She is afraid of death.
Do you hear what she is asking me?
She said, "These challenges. Do I mean that they will only attack us but will not kill us?"
Already, you have been having challenges. Even as you are standing now, you have challenges.
But those challenges have not killed you since. You are still alive.
Yes.
So why do you thing of death?
Because, maybe.....
Do you have a covenant?
No.
No, I was just thinking that, maybe if a challenge comes, like sickness to a loved one.
Do you mean that you have not been sick before?
I have.
That's it.
So thank you. You are clear. Ok, I like that.
Thank you, sir.
You have answered all my questions why I am here.
Now, since 2017 is a wonderful year, I love my nation Kenya. We are having elections
I am asking that you visit me in a dream, so that I know how to pray about my nation. God bless you, sir.
You want to take me back to what I have written there.
Even your country is one of the countries that is on that paper there.
If I may tell you just a bit of what is on that paper.
It will be very very close like this.
And it will be difficult to call. I will not say more than that.
Can you see, when something is close like this. And it will be difficult to call.
I don't want to go back to what is in the paper.
Because it is one of the things in the paper. It will be very close like this.
The opposition and the ruling. It will be very very difficult to call.
From there, more, I will not be able to say more than that. But I am not here for that now.
Therefore, what can you expect from there? So I will see you. Thank you.
So you love your nation so much?
The SCOAN Sunday Service